kabbalah.com 2014-12-22

# Privacy Policy | The Kabbalah Centre

**KABBALAH CENTRE INTERNATIONAL PRIVACY POLICY**

Kabbalah Centre International, Inc. (the “Centre”) is committed to protecting our users’ information and to making our users aware of our online practices regarding the privacy of your information.

By accessing our Web site maintained at [www.kabbalah.com](http://www.kabbalah.com/ "www.kabbalah.com") (the “Site”), you expressly consent and agree to the terms and conditions of this privacy policy, including our use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, then please do not use or access our Site.

**Information Collected**

Visitors to our Site can access the Site’s home page and browse the Site without disclosing any personally identifiable information depending on your privacy settings. We may track information provided to us by your browser, including the Web site you came from (known as the "referring URL"), the type of browser you use, the time and date of access, and other information that does not personally identify you.

The Centre may also collect personal information when you provide it to the Centre, such as registering as a user, signing up for a newsletter, making a purchase, participating in message boards or chat, participating in an online forum or other Site-based actions you decide to undertake.

Further to the extent that you post “User Content” (as defined in the [Terms of Use](http://www.kabbalah.com/terms)), and you identify yourself therein, you hereby authorize us to use your name, and any other personal information you provide with your User Content as further detailed in the [Terms of Use](http://www.kabbalah.com/terms).

**How the Information is Used**

The Centre may use the information you give it to provide services to you or provide information and notices that the Centre thinks you may find interesting or useful. The Centre may also use the information for confirmation of registrations, or other actions you take on our Site.

**Personal Information of Minors**

Therefore, the Centre Sites do not knowingly solicit or collect personally identifiable information online from children under the age of thirteen. If the Centre learns that a child under the age of thirteen has submitted personally identifiable information online, in contravention of these measures, it will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required by law).

**External Distribution of Personally Identifiable Information and of Confidential Information**

The Centre does not externally distribute personally-identifiable information of a user, except if a user specifically opts-in that certain of its personally-identifiable information be distributed to a third party, or if in connection with attribution for User Content contributed by you through the Site, including your use of Facebook Connect or other social media links. External distribution does not include certain limited distributions such as sharing personally-identifiable information with a third party working on behalf of the Centre, transfer of personally-identifiable information in connection with the sale of the Centre’s assets or the merger of the Centre or the disclosure of personally-identifiable information in connection with legal proceedings, investigations of crimes, or other governmental investigations. Transferring personally-identifiable information in connection with a sale or merger and sharing personally-identifiable information with an entity or person working on behalf of the Centre is considered an Onward Transfer to third parties and will be handled as described below.

**Use of Your Information to Protect the Centre and Others:**

We may release account and other personal information if we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our [Terms of Use](http://www.kabbalah.com/terms); or to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Centre, our other users, or third parties. This includes exchanging information with other companies and entities for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We do not, however, sell, rent, share, or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**Use of Cookies**

The Centre uses “cookies”. “Cookies” are elements of data that a Web site can send to a user’s browser and store on a user’s computer. Cookies do not contain personal information about a user. Cookies can note that a user’s browser was used to visit certain sites or pages on a certain date. The Centre uses cookies to enhance navigation and functionality of its Site. The Centre also uses cookies to let it know how visitors are using its Site, so that it can improve its Site and a user’s experience on it.

**Onward Transfer**

The transfer of personally-identifiable information to a third party in connection with a sale of assets of the Centre or a merger involving the Centre or the sharing of personally-identifiable information to a third party working on behalf of the Centre shall only be to a third party that (i) subscribes to the safe harbor principles of the U.S. Department of Commerce or is subject to the European Commission’s Directive on Data Protection, or (ii) has entered into a written agreement with the Centre requiring that such third party provides at least the same level of privacy protection as is required by the safe harbor principles.

**Security**

We have implemented technology and security policies, rules, and other measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, and accidental loss. We also protect your information by requiring that all our employees and others who have access to or are associated with the processing of your data respect your confidentiality. In addition, we have reasonable security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss or misuse of information at our site that we have collected from you.

**Access; Review and Correction**

Customers can, by e mailing us at [support@ukabbalah.com](mailto:support@ukabbalah.com) to review and correct the personally identifiable information that has been collected from them by this Site.

**Binding Agreement; Changes**

Any user that accesses all or any part of this Site agrees that such user is at least eighteen (18) years old, or has accessed this Site with the [consent of a parent or legal guardian](http://www.kabbalah.com/terms#minors) and that such user has consented to this Privacy Policy. Each time a user accesses this Site, this Privacy Policy should be reviewed because the Centre reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time without prior notice. Your use of our Site constitutes your acceptance of the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Link**

This Site may provide links to other Web sites that the Centre thinks you will find interesting or useful. The Centre is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites.

Last updated August, 2011.
